Tony Carbetta

Front End Web Developer

South San Francisco, CA 94080 ♦ (650) 270-7142 ♦ TonyCarbetta@gmail.com ◆ www.TonyCarbetta.com ◆ www.linkedin.com/in/tony-carbetta ◆ www.Github.com/TonyRuQusSCarbetta

While gaining a lot of web development experience in the last two years, my time at Coding Bootcamp Codify Academy is where I have excelled the most! I have mentors/colleagues/Github that can verify my talent, drive, and work. (especially with CSS, Bootstrap, Responsive Design, & Javascript) Prior to that I spent a year in multiple online bootcamps and completed 1,000's of hours worth of certified courses. My portfolio website displays work I've done. Thank you for the opportunity! I hope to hear from you soon.

Having an advanced level of skill and knowledge in many areas, I still find myself being an "advanced googler" everyday lol Any real developer knows how to be a Stack Overflow forum champion while digging for answers. While I can surely get the job done, I am constantly learning and can set the tone in a prospering work environment.

Works very well under pressure and in fast paced environments with strict deadlines. Extremely punctual & dependable. When things get rough I'm the one you can depend on to step up and get the job done.

Technical Toolbox

Web
Tools:

Javascript, Git/Github, Bootstrap4, CSS3, HTML5, Command Line Terminal, Gimp/Photoshop, Slack, creating responsive web sites/ apps/ services/ emails. I am briefly familiar with the REACT, ES6, Babel, Node, stack. Currently in the early learning stages of back end development with Node, PHP & My SQL.

Education

Codify Academy - San Francisco On-Site Coding Bootcamp

- Working everyday with Senior developers, colleagues, & team members on Slack
- Pushing, branching, and cloning projects daily on Github.
- Debugging and assisting other Jr Developer's projects when needed.
- Sharpening my current professional skills while developing new skills and learning new Frameworks.

Education (continued)

UDEMY - (1000'S OF HOURS WORTH OF WEB DEVELOPMENT ONLINE COURSES COMPLETED)

Certificates of completion

Courses:

- The Complete Web Developer Bootcamp in 2018: (with **REACT**)
 Andrei Neagoie
- Web Developer Boot Camp Colt Steele
- Bootstrap 4 Code Modern Responsive Websites – Brad Hussey
- Modern Javascript from the Beginning - Brad Traversy
- Web Hosting 101 Brad Hussey
- Ultimate Web Designer & Developer (Build 23 Real World Projects)
 Brad Hussey

Professional Experience

2016-present Carbetta Coding & Codify Academy San Francisco, CA

Web Developer

Specializing in front end development.

Take a PSD design and make it a dynamic web page/app.

Independently developed a dynamic, secure Web business from scratch. Launched visually appealing, user-friendly site with interactive features to optimize traffic, page views, and user experience (UX).

Provide complete Responsive Website/App launching services for any small business using best web practices programs and tools.

Regularly keep up with site maintenance, as projects are being completed and updated.

Create a positive customer service and sales experience with clients.

De-bug CSS, JavaScript, and html.

2010-present Sears San Mateo, CA

Large Appliance Salesman

SOLD OVER 1.2 MILLION DOLLARS in 2015!! (Gaining corporate recognition)

Started off knowing absolutely nothing about large appliances and within the first two months working full time commission sales, I earned Best of Blue awards for going above company standards and exceeding my sales goals.

Top performing salesman numerous months.

Started as a seasonal cashier, quickly became top performing full time cashier for two years. Than promptly promoted to selling big-ticket items in appliances.

2016-present Uber/Lyft Bay Area, CA

Driver

Provided flexible hours to pursue my education and Dream/Goal of launching my career as a Web Developer

Supplemented income when freelance projects were slow

Gave a deep understanding of the geography and culture of the Bay Area!

Over 1,000 ride given to date

Assistant Manager

Managed staff in concessions, usher, and projection!

Delegate staff, ensure appropriate breaks, payroll, change over, (built, broke-down and shipped films weekly as they arrived or left)

Head of the Usher Department, with a group of ushers cleaning theatres as they let out, delegating lines, and handling ANY customer service within the building.

2006-2008 Calvary Family Martial Arts & Fitness Colorado Springs, CO

Assistant Junior Instructor

Excelled in physical fitness, instruction, and labor

Taught youth of all ages, focusing on developing confidence, self worth, and integrity as well as the importance of defending one's self

2006-2007 <u>Safeway/Starbucks</u> Colorado Springs, CO

Barista

Served drinks to various amounts of people

Opened & closed store, ordered appropriate supplies, expanded sales, announced special promotions and trained new employees.

Earned three pins for being accredited 100% on secret shoppers.

2004-2006 Subway Sandwiches Colorado Springs, CO

Shift Supervisor

Ensured complete customer satisfaction

Responsibilities included training new employees, closing the store, making sure prep work was done for morning crew, and all employees had appropriate breaks.

Completely turned the night crew around to a positive customer friendly environment.

References are 100% available upon request.